今天我们主要的内容是来讲如何制作折剪,并且制作一件衬衫和colorway该如何使用。
这次直播的素材呢,大家可以到微信公众号后台回复链接就可以拿到了。
大家也可以关注我们的微博,可以给我们发送大家的作品。
现在我们将这次的素材给打开。
从素材中找到这一个折件的素材,将它双击打开。
我们先将涂布窗口收起来。
现在我们先将目光放到这一个大的长方形板片上。
我们需要将这一个长方形板片制作成一个正方体。
那么我们该如何来折叠这一个内部线呢?
我们可以在3D工具栏中选择折叠安排工具。
在第一条内部线上左键单击。
这时我们就可以看到在内部线上有两个箭头。
我们将鼠标放到需要折叠的那一边的箭头上。
按住鼠标左键并且移动鼠标。
现在我们就可以看到这一个板片被折叠了。
那么我们将目光移到我们的属性编辑器中。
我们可以看到被选中的这一个内部线它的折叠角度变为了180度。
变成了84度。
而没有被选中的内部线它们的折叠角度为180度。
现在我们再来使用折叠安排工具将另外两条内部线折叠。
折叠好之后我们来进行缝纫将它变成一个正方体。
也可以在3D窗口中进行缝纫。
至于它的缝纫线方向。
也可以在2D窗口中进行缝纫。
再缝合结束之后我们打开模拟。
再缝合结束之后,将它变成为D恤镰。
但是就这样入墟。
现在这种 cheek use it and then put it in.
在这里处理一下。
现在我已经把可以把这个 strongly away from the edge.
在这里处理一下和它就比较いい。
Select the border line tool and select the border line.
In the property border machine, we can see that there is a folding angle at the bottom of the border line type.
We can also set the folding angle of the border line.
We set its angle to 90 degrees.
In this simulation, we can see that the edge of the border line is as smooth as the edge of the inner line.
Now we set the angle of the remaining border line to 90 degrees.
Open the simulation.
Now we can see that this square is relatively smooth.
That's it.
We'll now look at the folding angle.
In the folding angle, we press the right button to activate the folding angle.
When we set an angle to the vertical angle,
As you can see, there are only two sides.
Now let's fold and sew the waist.
Using the sewing machine, we can sew the 3D window.
Open the model after sewing.
When we turn the model to the back,
we can see that the fold is dropped.
Now we need to sew the fold to the fold.
We can also sew the 3D window.
We need to sew the fold to both sides.
Open the model.
Now we can see that the fold is sewed.
How to sew the fold to the fold?
We can see a blue dot on the 2D panel.
We can also see a blue dot on the 2D panel.
This means that the blue dot is the sewing line.
We can use the sewing machine to sew the fold again.
We need to pay attention to the sewing line.
Open the model.
Here we can see that the fold is open.
How to make it smoother?
We can use the foldable sewing machine.
Select the foldable sewing machine we just added.
In the model, the sewing line type.
Open the side triangle.
Change the sewing line type to Tung.
This way, the fold will be smoother.
Close the model.
This is the fold.
Now we can make a shirt.
Open the DxF document of the shirt.
No need to save it.
Click OK.
We just need to open the reflection of the shirt.
Open the photo of a model.
Now we can see that the fold is plenty.
To do this, we need to put the shoukufu and the shouchatiao next to the shouzi.
Put the back of the shoukufu and the shouchatiao on top of the back of the shouzi.
After arranging, put all the shoukufu and the shouchatiao around the model shadow.
Now let's copy the other half of the shoukufu.
Select the tool to edit the shoukufu.
On the back middle line, right-click and select .
Open both the shoukufu and the shouchatiao.
Select the tool to adjust the shoukufu.
Right-click on the shoukufu.
In the menu, select .
Press and hold the shift key to move the shoukufu to the other side.
Let's not do the alignment of the shoukufu and the shouchatiao.
Let's rearrange the 2D window to 3D window.
Now let's open the model's arrangement.
In the tool bar,
select the 4th one and select .
You can also press and hold the shift key to open the arrangement.
Now let's move the shoukufu to the top.
Because there is a layer relationship between the front and the back of the shoukufu,
the front of the shoukufu is on the top of the left front.
So we need to move the front of the shoukufu to the top of the left front.
Now let's right-click the front of the shoukufu.
Now let's right-click the front of the shoukufu to the top of the left front.
Once we're done.
Use this tool
Move the left front to the top of the right front.
Move the right front up to the left front.
Similarly, there is also a layer relationship between the shoukufu and the shoukufu.
Here we can see the gap between them in the rotation view.
Now let's do the group arrangement.
We select two front pieces at the same time.
Place it on the model's arrangement point.
Select the sleeve and the sleeve insert at the same time.
Arrange the sleeve joint.
Arrange the back piece.
Arrange the sleeve.
After arranging, we will close the arrangement point.
We can press the shift key to close the arrangement point.
Now let's do the sewing.
In the process of sewing, pay attention to the direction of the sewing line.
If the seam is wrong, the seam will be wrong.
Then you can use the
right-click to switch the sewing line.
Now let's show the seam difference.
In the 2D tool bar, click on the circle tool and press the shortcut key.
Select the line that indicates the seam difference.
On the basic line, right-click and select Cut in the menu.
Now the line is cut.
Now let's use the editor tool to adjust the opening and closing distance.
Again, select the line that indicates the seam difference.
You can press Shift to select multiple lines and press the reverse button to select them.
Now let's sew the seam line onto the sleeve.
You can use the free sewing tool to do this.
Note that one side of the seam line is open, so you don't need to sew the seam line.
Now let's sew the sleeve to the sleeve.
Use the free sewing tool to select the first seam line from the right to the left.
Press Shift to start sewing from the seam line.
On the sleeve,
you can see that the seam line has been folded.
So start sewing from the seam line.
We need to fold the seam line later on, so start sewing from the seam line.
Loosen Shift and the seam line is sewed.
Now let's show the seam line.
You can use the circle tool to select the seam line.
Press Shift to select the second seam line.
Press the reverse button to select the seam line.
On the left side of the seam line, set the fold angle to 0 degrees.
On the right side of the seam line, set the fold angle to 360 degrees.
Now start sewing the seam line.
We need to sew the seam line on both sides of the seam line.
The seam line direction needs to be relative.
So let's change the seam line type to Tint.
You also need to sew the seam line on both sides of the seam line.
The seam line type needs to be changed.
Now let's add a button to the shirt.
You can choose the button tool from the 3D tool bar.
On the left front,
On the left-hand side of the base line of the button,
we can create a button.
We can rotate the view to see that there is a button in the 3D window.
We can also use the right-hand button on the board to create a contrast.
We can choose the position of the button here.
We can also position the button between the boards.
Click OK.
Now let's add a button.
On the left-hand side of the base line of the button,
we can rotate the view to see that there is a button.
We can create a button.
We can also rotate the view to see that there is a button on the 3D window.
We can also create a button.
Click OK.
Now let's use the move button.
In the 3D window,
select this button and move the mouse.
We can move the button.
We can also move it in the 2D window.
Now click on the button on the left-hand side of the second button.
Click on the button on the right-hand side of the button.
We can copy it.
Click on the button on the right-hand side of the button to paste it.
We can see that there is a button.
As the mouse moves,
it appears.
We can put this button in the 3D window.
Click on the button on the left-hand side of the button and put it there.
We can also do the same.
Click on the button on the right-hand side of the button.
A dialogue box will pop up.
We can enter the distance of the button here.
And the number of buttons needed for the button.
Now we enter the number 5 here.
Click OK.
Now all the buttons are added at once.
Now we can click on the button on the right-hand side of the button.
At the bottom, there is a copy and paste version of the symmetrical modification.
And paste the button to the symmetrical version.
We first select the first copy and paste version of the symmetrical modification.
We can see that
there appears a copy on the symmetrical version.
Now we choose the left-hand side of the button.
And paste the button to the window of the symmetrical version.
Here we can see that there appears a copy in the symmetrical version.
Now we75SE哪個本該
So what can we do?
Click on the right-hand back of the button on the right-hand side of the button.
We can convert it to the button.
We can select the frame.
and select the rest of the buckles.
Right-click on the buckles,
and copy the buckles to the symmetrical panel.
Now we have added all the buckles at once.
Now let's add the buckles on the sleeve and collar.
We can see that when we add the buckles on the collar,
the base line of the buckles is a diagonal line.
So how do we align the buckles with the base line?
We select the move button here,
and click on the buckles.
We can set the angle in the parameter editor.
We can also set the angle of the buckles
by clicking on the buckles on the parameter editor.
Now let's close the buckles.
We can click on the buckles
in the 3D window,
and then click on the buckles.
Now we can close the buckles.
We can also close the buckles
in the 3D window.
We can also select all the buckles
by clicking on the buckles.
in the 3D window.
Once the buckles are closed,
Now we are going to adjust the position of the collar.
We can click on the collar.
In the property editor, we can reduce the diameter.
Reduce it to the front and middle overlap.
We need the right side to be on the top.
Now the left side is on the top.
We can right-click on the collar.
There will be a rotation to the direction of the package.
Select this option to rotate the direction of the package.
There is also a cut-off sound.
Now we are going to make the collar.
We can use the edit tool.
Right-click on the bottom line of the collar.
Select the internal line.
We select 5 for the border line.
Click OK.
Now we are going to use the fold adjustment tool.
Select the inner line on the collar.
Turn the collar over.
Then we need to select the inner line of the collar in the 2D window.
Adjust the fold angle to 300.
Then we need to adjust the fold angle to 360.
After adjusting, we can open the model.
Now we are going to use the edit tool in the 2D window.
Select the sleeve, the sleeve insert and the sleeve opening.
Right-click on the button.
Select the symmetrical sleeve, the sleeve and the seam line.
Put it on the other side.
We can see that there is a sleeve in the 3D window.
The shape of the sleeve on the left side is the same.
Now we are going to use the position tool.
Put the sleeve on the model's arm.
Now we are going to close the button.
If you see that there is a problem with the direction of the button,
then we can select it.
Then we can rerun the 3D position arrangement,
and simulate it.
Then we can simulate it.
Now we change the model's pose to the front-facing pose.
Change the material.
Open the model again.
Now let's make the collar of this shirt.
We can use the hook and loop tool to cut and sew the collar.
Open the model again.
We can see that the collar and the shirt are automatically sewed together.
Now let's make the collar of this shirt.
Pull the material to the bottom.
Make a small triangle at the hip.
Select the hip.
Open the model again.
We can see that the collar is thickened at the upper side of the material.
Remember that.
We need to increase the thickness of the membrane here.
Let's take a look at the thickness of the fabric we added.
We choose this piece of fabric at the bottom of the window.
At the bottom of the parameter editor, we can see that its thickness is 0.32 mm.
We also increase the thickness of the membrane by 0.32 mm.
We can see that the membrane has changed thickness.
We also pull the parameter editor to the top, and choose the double layer.
This way, the membrane will show the double layer effect.
We also need to increase the thickness of the collar and the sleeve.
We also increase the thickness of the membrane by 0.32 mm.
We also increase the thickness of the collar and the sleeve.
We also pull the parameter editor to the top, and choose the double layer effect.
Now let's increase the thickness of the collar and the sleeve.
When we increase the thickness, we can use the SATA editor to tune the size and direction.
After tuning, we select the button button option layer in Autoensitive window,
click the button to click.
We can see in the parameter editor the button name.
Now we see in the parameter editor the button name.
Open the triangle next to the shape.
We can change the type of the screw here.
We can also change the size of the screw.
The thickness.
And its weight.
We can also change the type of the screw.
There are also some types of metal.
We can also add a texture to the screw.
We can also change the color of the screw.
Now we select the eye in the object window.
We can also see the name of the eye in the attribute editor.
We can also change its shape.
And its size.
Including its attribute type.
And its color.
Now we select the eye in the object window.
We can also add and copy two buttons here.
And a user.
Add and copy is the same as the material window.
And the user.
We'll select.
Partial screws.
Click action.
Click user.
Here we can see.
The same, what it adds it is also a default.
Screw.
We can also change it.
Change its type.
color, and size.
Now let's make the colorway.
Move the mouse to the mode.
Open the triangle next to the model.
Click on the flag.
Here we can enter the multi-format edit window.
In the upper right corner,
there is a plus button.
Click on this plus button.
You can add a style.
Enter its name here.
Click OK.
We can change its texture here.
We can also change
the color of the curve.
We can also change its type of face.
We can also change its color.
Click on the update button.
Now in our multi-format edit window,
there will be two different costumes.
They are just different in texture and appearance.
Now here we can change its texture and appearance.
Here we can change its color.
There is a list here.
We can also change their color.
Next we will move on to their outfit.
For the outfit,
we are going to write our outfit.
Go to our outfit.
Go to the outfit.
You can also change the style.
There is a new file in our material package.
Let's open it up.
Let's use it first.
Select the 3D window in the file section.
Enter its name.
Click Save.
You can change its size and direction here.
You can also choose a transparent background.
Click Save.
After saving, let's click on the star on the left.
Use the positioning tool to lay the star flat.
Set it to 3D.
Select the 3D window in the middle of the grid.
Click on the model and place it at the bottom.
Close the model.
Now let's choose this Samsung version.
Click on the file.
Select the one you want to export to OBG.
Enter its name here.
Click Save.
You don't need to make any changes here.
Just click OK.
Now let's go back to our outfit.
Click on the button.
Select any button in the 3D window.
Under the model, click the plus sign.
Click on the plus sign.
A dialogue box will pop out.
Click on the plus sign in the
Inputs box.
The saved image will be added to the saved image.
The same thing goes for OBG.
Click Save.
Open the saved .obj file, click OK, click OK.
Now we can adjust its size.
Now the .obj button is done.
You can also change its color here to make it more stable.
After that, we can choose to increase the quality of the clothing.
Click OK.
And we can start the simulation.
So that's all for this live stream.
Now let's move on to the Q&A session.
If you have any questions,
you can ask them in the Q&A section.
Now you can start the Q&A session.
Click OK,
After that we can switch on live streaming.
If you want live streaming is good,
or you want tears,
it's up to you.
Now the Q&A session starts.
Hello, this is the Q&A session and back to live streaming.
The Q&A session is still please,
Once the Q&A session is end,
we will notice that the Q&A session is 벌써开始,
All right, here we go.
想看走秀啊,这个可以时刻关注着我们的微信公众号,我们每一周都会发布我们要直播什么哦,贴图制作。
我们在前几期已经讲过贴图制作咯,可以去看一下我们的回放。
现在的最新版是多少?
现在最新版本是5.2.172。
素材可以去我们的微信公众号,后台回复链接就有了。
双层面料的话,我里面的面料总是出来。
那你可以使用层次设定。
我们在属性编辑器中这里有一个层。
扭扣类型里面的内容可以再讲一下吗?
扭扣类型,扭扣的类型和我们上一次讲的面料类型是一样的哦。
不ウ十是个分代后。
大家还有什么问题吗?
If you have any questions, feel free to contact us via our WeChat official account, and we will reply to your questions.
We also have links to our previous posts on our WeChat official account.
You can take a closer look at our posts every time.
What does it mean by only rendering?
It means that only when rendering is started, will the image appear.
The image will be shown as a double-layer image.
How do you change the color of the zipper?
If you cannot do it, can you show us?
Let me show you again.
Yes, our little C-Jun has already answered this question.
C-Jun has already answered this question.
We will render the same colored zipper face.
You can change the texture or color of the zipper face.
I'm done here.
Thank you for watching.
See you next time.
Thank you.
Our little C-Jun is still here.
If you have any questions, you can ask.
If you don't ask, we're going to end.
Remember to follow our WeChat official account.
This way you can get our live broadcast information accurately.
Of course, you have to pay close attention to our live broadcasts.
Maybe there will be a winner.
I love you, little C-Jun.
Do you love me?
Your voice is so sweet.
You're sweeter.
Why don't you answer the question?
What's your question?
Let me see.
Do you have any questions for big C-Jun?
I'm impossible to answer with one word.
SaidCện together with the crowd.
HA transition ZG in over five seconds!
You can do better than big C-Jun.
How's it going to be with big C-Jun?
See you later.
Good, quickly.
Bye-bye.
You can take a look.
Can Cy Rut 스읍ative Look at you?
Our small細菌 هي我們的寶貝, Don't show this to you!
Our data can be found at WeChat.
You can also get it in the post consistent Request to connect
can be obtained.
大家还有没有问题呢? Do you have any more questions?
下次啥时候上课啊? When is the next class?
这次没有赶上 I didn't catch up this time.
可以时刻关注我们的 You can always pay attention to our
微信公众号,这样就可以了,实时获得我们的直播时间咯. WeChat public number, so you can get our live broadcast time on time.
大家还有问题吗? Do you have any more questions?
怎样可以让渲染快一点? How can we speed up the blood circulation?
可以让电脑的配置好一点呀? How can we make the computer configuration better?
球怎么做? How to make the ball?
我们的球体是不可以做到,但是可以做圆柱体。 Our ball can't be made, but it can be made into a cylinder.
我们会在4月。 We will be in April.
我们会在4月28号的下午进行我们的5.2新功能直播。 On the afternoon of April 28, we will do our 5.2 live broadcast.
大家如果有空的话,可以来看一看哦。 If you have time, you can come and have a look.
我们会在4月28号的下午3点中进行新功能直播。 We will do our 5.2 live broadcast on the afternoon of April 28.
大家可以都过来看一看。 You can all come and have a look.
你们回家吧,太晚了。 Go home, it's too late.
谢谢小小丸子爱吃肉,对我们的关心。 Thank you, little balls, for loving meat and caring about us.
大家可以点击一下,关注一下我们的bilibili账号,这样子可以准时的获得我们的直播信息哦。 You can click and follow our Bilibili account so that you can get our live broadcast information on time.
三地窗口粘秤的颜色怎么去掉。 How to remove the color of the 3D window.
我们可以将鼠标悬停到三地窗口垂直栏的第三个,有一个显示粘秤或者是消保,将它点掉就不会有了。 We can move the mouse to the third one of the 3D window. If there is a display粘秤或者是消保,将它点掉就不会有了。 If there is a display粘秤或者是消保, just remove it.
主播们吃饭了吗?主播还没有吃饭呢。好饿哦。 Have the streamers eaten yet? The streamers haven't eaten yet. I'm so hungry.
快要九点咯,到九点钟我们就直播结束咯。 It's almost nine o'clock. We'll end the live broadcast at nine o'clock.
大家抓紧哦,已经九点了。 Oh, it's already nine o'clock.
大家没有问题我们就要回家咯。 If you have no questions, we'll go home.
那今天我们的直播就到这里了。 That's all for today's live broadcast.
很感谢大家这一次的到来。 Thank you for coming.
希望大家可以关注我们的微信公众号。 I hope you can follow our WeChat official account.
这样就可以实时获得我们的直播信息。 So you can get our live broadcast information on time.
也可以在微信公众号回复一些问题,我们也会回答的。 You can also reply to some questions on WeChat official account.
同样也可以将自己的作品发到我们的官方微博上面给我们。 You can also send your works to our official Weibo.
谢谢大家。 Thank you.
好,大家再见哦。 Bye bye.